sutradara.info 2011-04-23

# Privacy Policy on Cdnpages

**Privacy Policy  **

Cdnpages is a web based application which allows users to search for business information based on a number of criteria.Our company may add or edit information, images, or video associated with businesses. This information can be accessed by anyone with an Internet connection. Cdnpages is committed to controlling the collection ,use and disclosure of the personal information provided by its customers.This Privacy ensures the accuracy, confidentiality and integrity of your personal information.Your privacy is important to us.Cdnpages respects and takes steps to protect the privacy of our customers.We strive to take reasonable care of information we may receive from you.

**Respecting and Protecting your Privacy  **

Cdnpages will not sell or share personally identifiable information of its individual customers to third parties without the prior permission of the user. Users who wish to use our enhanced or personalized services may be required to provide additional information. By voluntarily providing more personal information you allow us to increase the value of your experience on our site. Cdnpages will use the data collectively for its own statistical analyses of its services. Cdnpages may also ask users to complete surveys for research purposes only. All demographic and behavioural research is compiled on an aggregated basis and would only be shared in aggregate form to interested third parties. By providing an e-mail address, a user may from time to time receive communications from Cdnpages on its new products and services or special offers that may be of interest. 

Cdnpages reserves the right to change its policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement does not create any contractual rights on behalf of any party. You agree that Cdnpages has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor the Cdnpages Sites and the Services electronically from time to time and to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or other governmental request, to operate a Cdnpages or any of the Services properly, or to protect itself or its users.

You acknowledge that in the event that a third party service provider is located in foreign country, your personal information may be processed and stored in any other country, and the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of that country may be able to obtain disclosure of your personal information through the laws of the foreign country. Whenever we engage a third party service provider to do work for us, we confirm that its privacy and security standards meet our requirements. You acknowledge and agree that this paragraph constitutes prior written notice to you of, and your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described above. Cdnpages collects personal information for specific, limited purposes. Information is collected by fair and lawful means. 

Cdnpages collects some personal information, such as your name and email address, from you to provide the requested service. Cdnpages does not sell, share, or rent your personal information in ways different from what is disclosed here. Cdnpages may also use third-party companies to provide various services when you visit this website. Cdnpages is not responsible for the privacy practices of external websites linked to this site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites when you leave our website. 

When you voluntarily disclose information on the public forums of this site, your personal and other information disclosed in your communication shall become public information and can be collected and used by outside parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Cdnpages. If you enter a contest or other promotion, we use your personal contact information to administer the contest or promotion, including contacting, announcing and promoting prizewinners.

**Cookies  **

A cookie is a small file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer, ready for future access when you return to our site. The websites use a browser feature called a "cookie" to collect information anonymously and track user patterns on Cdnpages websites. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a website. "Cookies" contain a unique identification number that identifies your browser, but not you, to our computers each time you visit one of our websites. Cookies tell us which pages of our websites are visited and by how many people. 

The use of cookies is an industry standard and many major browsers are initially set up to accept them. You can reset your browser to either refuse to accept all cookies or to notify you when you have received a cookie. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on our websites. The user identification Cookie will remain until the user signs off and clears it from their computer. 

We may use cookies to tailor and improve the content we deliver to you while you are on our site. The cookies do not contain or capture any personal information. You can configure your computer's browser to alert you when a site is attempting to send you a cookie, and then you can accept or refuse the cookie. Your decision to refuse cookies from Cdnpages will not prevent you from using our site, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of our advanced features.

We use cookie technology to track which pages on the Cdnpages site our visitors view and which Web browsers our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help you perform searches on the Cdnpagese efficiently and more effectively. This may include the storing of your previous search terms in cookies. 

Our partners or advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit our site. Any third party cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the company placing them. Some Internet browsers allow you to opt out of third party cookies. For more information about opting out of third party cookies, follow your Internet browse help file directions.

**Legal Notice  **

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ALL INFORMATION, SERVICES, AND CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITH NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING: CDNPAGES MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT ANY INFORMATION OR CONTENT PROVIDED HEREIN IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE, OR AUTHENTIC; AND CDNPAGES SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR INFORMATION OR CONTENT PROVIDED BY THIRD PARTIES. CDNPAGES RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MODIFY ANY INFORMATION, CONTENT OR SERVICES AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.

**Personal information  **

Your profile, photos, videos, and any personally identifiable information will be posted on this site for users to see. 

Your email address may also be used and disclosed to your friends when you use this site to send an email to your friends to share site information, or invite them to join the site. If your friends use this site to contact you, we will use your name and email address to contact you on behalf of your friends. 

Cdnpages may transfer your personal information to affiliates and service providers acting on its behalf for internal audit, management, administrative and other purposes or in order to perform processing and other specialized services, such as prize fulfillment of our contests. 

Cdnpages will disclose your personal information to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal processes. We also reserve the right to use and disclose your personal information where required or permitted by law or if we have reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial or foreign law, in order to protect or defend our legal interests, or to comply with applicable laws and lawful governmental requests. 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Cdnpages’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Cdnpages may disclose your personal information to parties connected with the contemplated or actual financing, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of our business or assets, including for the purposes of determining whether to proceed or continue with such transaction or business relationship or fulfilling any records or other reporting requirements to such parties. We will require such parties to treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and to use and disclose only for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Non-Personal Information:  **

Non-personal or aggregated information is information that cannot be associated with or traced back to a specific person. When you browse this site and are not logged in, for example, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you, but we do gather information about the number of people viewing each page so that we can learn what features are the most popular. We also collect the IP addresses of all visitors to the site. We disclose aggregated information about this website to third parties. 

Online Policy Regarding Privacy of Children: We do not believe that this website appeals directly to individuals under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect information from individuals under this age. Please do not use this site if you are under the age of 18. Cdnpages urges all parents to supervise their children’s exploration of the Internet and any online services and to teach their children about protecting their personal information online.

Generally, by providing us with your personal information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to collect, use and disclose your personal information without consent where required or permitted by law. If you do not wish you can let us know by sending an email to admin@cdnpages.ca .

How to Access and Modify Your Personal Information: If you want to modify your personal/business information you can e-mail us at admin@cdnpages.ca . Contact Information: If you have any questions or comments about Cdnpages Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, you can contact at admin@cdnpages.ca 

**Information Are Not Sold or Distributed  **

Information provided will not be resold or distributed to mail-order list providers or others. Be aware, however, that information you provide and make public is available to Cdnpages users as well as to commercial organizations. Cdnpages will not disclose or share your e-mail address or personal information with others except to provide products and services requested for or to perform and to monitor the use of services. We may use aggregated information concerning how visitors use our Web site and share such information with third parties in order to improve our Web site and to help us attract advertisers and listings. For example, we may share how many individuals visited our Web site and on average how long they stayed on each page. Such use and sharing of aggregated information will not reveal any of your personal information to third parties.

**Third Party Advertisers and External Links  **

Cdnpages Web site may accept advertisements from third-party advertisers or provide links to external Web sites. Please check the privacy policy of these advertisers and sites for information regarding their collection of information and use of cookies. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other Web sites. Our partners or advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit our site. Any third party cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the company placing them.

**Accuracy  **

Cdnpages will try to ensure that information about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, please inform the Cdnpages to whom you provided your information of any change of name, address or other information. In the event you have questions about the accuracy of factual information we have collected about you, you will have access to that information in order to verify and update it. If we have disclosed inaccurate information about you to a third party, we will be pleased to contact the third party in order to correct the information. 

**Security  **

Cdnpages.ca takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your information. No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Cdnpages.ca maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

Ads On Cdnpages:--  
[Job vacancies](http://www.intljobs.org/):- Job vacancies search at international organizations.
